inthepowderroom.com 2018-03-27

# Privacy Policy | In the Powder Room

### Your Privacy and the Security of Your Personal Information Is Very Important to Us

Hold My Purse Productions LLC (“HMPP”) doing business at www.inthepowderroom.com values our customers and guests and respects your concerns about online security and privacy. We believe in providing you with a safe and secure time while experiencing the editorial and community aspects of our site. Our Privacy and Security Policy is intended to protect your privacy and ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information. In addition to reviewing our Privacy and Security Policy, you should also read our Terms of Use. Your use of www.inthepowderroom.com constitutes your agreement to its terms and conditions.

##### Our Privacy and Security Policy Will Change Over Time

Because we continue to develop www.inthepowderroom.com and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide our users, our policies will change over time. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy and Security Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices. If you are a registered member of www.inthepowderroom.com, we may notify you by e-mail of material changes to our Privacy and Security Policy using the most current e-mail address that you have provided to us. Your continued access and use of www.inthepowderroom.com will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy and Security Policy.

##### Summary of Our Privacy and Security Policy

This Privacy and Security Policy explains and summarizes how we collect, use, and protect your personal information as you interact with us online and through our customer and technical support. This Privacy and Security Policy explains:

  * What information HMPP gathers from users of www.inthepowderroom.com.
  * How HMPP uses the personal information that you share with us and that we learn about you because of our relationship.
  * How HMPP uses “cookies” and “IP Addresses.”
  * What personal information, if any, HMPP may share about you with others and the conditions that protect your information if it is or must be shared.
  * What kind of security measures HMPP takes to protect your information from loss or disclosure and how HMPP will inform you in the event of a security breach.
  * The circumstances under which you can access your personal information you have shared with HMPP and have that information corrected, restrict HMPP’s use of that information, and even have it removed from our records.
  * Other things you should know about privacy and HMPP.

##### The Type of Information www.inthepowderroom.com Collects About You

HMPP collects information that you provide to us or that we learn about you from your use of www.inthepowderroom.com. We receive and store information you enter on www.inthepowderroom.com or give to us in any other way. For example, you may provide information to www.inthepowderroom.com when you register, sign-in, search, participate in a poll or survey, request our e-mail newsletters, or communicate with HMPP’s customer service. As a result of those actions, you **might** supply us with such information as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, likes, dislikes and other preferences (although, currently, most of this information is not required to use our site). We also automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit www.inthepowderroom.com. We might also receive information about you from other sources, such as in providing you special offers that we think will be of interest, and we may add that information to our account information for you.

##### How HMPP Uses Information About You

We use information we have collected about you to provide you with the most relevant and entertaining articles, videos and other forms of entertaining content. **We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason.** We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so.

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of HMPP where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction or do something you have asked us to do. Currently HMPP does not provide shopping services but it may in the future and this information may be shared with a retailer or product provider, upon your request, to complete such a transaction with that third party.

We may share your personal information to third parties or affiliates of HMPP with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform.

We may disclose personal information about our customers as permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, or in connection with a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy, as discussed further below.

We try to provide you with the information you need to make informed and reasonable choices with respect to how www.inthepowderroom.com uses or shares your information. HMPP collects and uses personal information from you in several ways:

**Website Usage.  ** HMPP or HMPP’s authorized service providers may observe activities, preferences, and transactional data (such as your IP address, browser type, and operating system) relating to your use of www.inthepowderroom.com. We may use this collected or logged information in order to provide better service, to facilitate our customers’ use of the website, to track usage of the website, and to address security hazards. HMPP, or one of HMPP’s authorized service providers, may use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout www.inthepowderroom.com. We may use aggregated, statistical information to describe our customer audience, products and services, and to develop partnerships with third parties to offer products and services in which we believe our customers will be interested. For example, if thirty percent of our customers are interested in new cars, we may share that statistic with automobile advertisers in order to offer through www.inthepowderroom.com the type of access, through advertisements, our users prefer.

**Site Interactions.** We collect information about you when you use our website. You may visit our site without registering, but if you wish to use certain special features offered on our site, you will need to provide us with certain information, including your name, address, and e-mail address, to register with us. We will assist you in creating a user ID and a password to protect your account information. If you provide to us information about a friend through the “Share with a Friend” section of www.inthepowderroom.com, we will first contact that friend by e-mail to confirm that the friend wishes to participate in www.inthepowderroom.com activities and consents to having personal information about him or her collected and retained by www.inthepowderroom.com. If your friend does not consent to our use of his or her contact information, we will delete it from our records.

**Forums, Comment Boards, Video Uploads.** Any information disclosed in public areas of www.inthepowderroom.com is public information that may be viewed and collected by any party. We cannot control the use of information disclosed in the social networking, comment boards, profile pages or other public portions of our site. You should exercise caution when disclosing information, including photos or images, in these public areas and should refrain from disclosing personally identifying information. If you wish to use some of the public portions on our site, we will direct you to first create a public ID before you can post information to our site. HMPP reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to remove any information at any time from our site that we deem inappropriate, objectionable or for any other reason.

##### Our Security Practices

Our internal data security policies restrict access to users’ personal information to authorized employees. Authorized employees may use our users’ personal information for HMPP business purposes only. Our employees are bound by HMPP policies that require them to maintain the confidentiality of our users’ personal information. Employees who violate these requirements are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard our customers’ personal information. For example, for the security of your online visit to www.inthepowderroom.com, we may make use of firewall barriers, encryption techniques, and/or authentication procedures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, HMPP cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your personal information, we will notify you as necessary so you can take appropriate protective steps. Unless you indicate otherwise, we may notify you under such circumstances using the e-mail address you provided to us when you registered with www.inthepowderroom.com.

##### **What Are Cookies and How Does Www.inthepowderroom.com Use Them?**

We may use “cookies” to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. We may use cookies for some administrative purposes—for example, to store our users’ preferences for certain kinds of stories or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our website. The cookies will not contain information that will enable anyone to contact our users via telephone, e-mail, or any other means. If our users are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, they can set their browsers to refuse cookies. Certain of our services, however, could be dependent on cookies, and our users may disable those services by refusing cookies.

Please note that the advertising networks serving ads on www.inthepowderroom.com may also use their own cookies. HMPP does not control these cookies or the data collection practices of these companies. For more information about these companies’ separate privacy policies, you should contact the advertising network directly. For more information on the privacy policies of our advertisers, see below.

##### **What Privacy Policies Cover the Ads on www.inthepowderroom.com?**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on www.inthepowderroom.com. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single-pixel GIFs or Web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is not connected to personally identifiable information, such as your name and e-mail address.

##### **Links to Third-Party Sites and Websites Containing www.inthepowderroom.com Branding**

www.inthepowderroom.com may contain links to third-party sites. Please be aware, however, that HMPP is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other sites or their practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours.

This website may also contain links to sites that display www.inthepowderroom.com branding and/or HMPP’s logo but which are maintained by third parties. Such websites may be identified in that they do not display a “www.inthepowderroom.com” URL. Please read the privacy policy on these sites for applicable privacy practices relating to personal information collected via those sites because they may differ from www.inthepowderroom.com’s privacy practices. This Privacy and Security Policy applies solely to personal information collected by HMPP at www.inthepowderroom.com.

##### **Contact Preferences and Accessing Your Personal Information**

You have choices when it comes to how HMPP uses your personal information. When you register online with www.inthepowderroom.com, you can choose not to receive information about our services, content and or special promotional items from us by direct mail and/or e-mail. If you elect not to receive such information by direct mail or e-mail, HMPP may continue to contact you as necessary to service your account. [You can change your contact preferences at any time by following the instructions for “My Powder Room” on www.inthepowderroom.com.]

Keeping your account information accurate and up-to-date is very important, so we can provide you with excellent service. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate, or not current, please follow the instructions for My Powder Room on www.inthepowderroom.com to correct your account information online.

If you need additional assistance, [please contact our customer service department.](mailto:info@inthepowderroom.com)

##### **This Privacy and Security Policy Applies to U.S. and U.K. Customers**

www.inthepowderroom.com is hosted in the United States and is intended for visitors from the United States, United Kingdom and other English speaking territories and countries.

This Privacy and Security Policy applies to customer relationships established in the United States and United Kingdom. Parts of this Privacy and Security Policy may not apply to visitors outside these territories. Like almost every website, www.inthepowderroom.com may be accessed by an international audience. If you are a non-U.S. or U.K. visitor to our website, by visiting our website and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in this Privacy and Security Policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction, which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By providing us with your data, you consent to transfer of such data.

##### **Mergers, Acquisitions, and Bankruptcy**

If HMPP should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, or if HMPP should decide to buy another business or sell or reorganize part or all of HMPP’s business, HMPP may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers and other parties. It is HMPP’s practice to obtain appropriate protections for information disclosed in these types of transactions. HMPP cannot, however, guarantee that HMPP’s Privacy and Security Policy will remain unchanged if HMPP is sold or merges with another company.

##### **www.inthepowderroom.com Is Not for Use by Children**

Children are not eligible to use www.inthepowderroom.com. We ask that minors (under the age of 18) only use www.inthepowderroom.com in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Children under 18 should not send any information about themselves to HMPP. If a child under 18 submits information through any part of www.inthepowderroom.com, and HMPP becomes aware that the person submitting the information is a child, we will attempt to delete this information as soon as possible. Because we do not knowingly collect any personal information about children under 18, we do not use or disclose such information to third parties.

##### **What Else Should I Know About My Privacy?**

You should be careful to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity whenever you are online.

##### Trademark Notice

HMPP and www.inthepowderroom.com are trademarks of Hold My Purse Productions, LLC.

**www.inthepowderroom.com  
**Hold My Purse Productions, LLC  
A Leslie Marinelli Joint  
4920 Atlanta Highway, Suite 327  
Alpharetta, GA  30004
